<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | My Website</title>
    <link>https://ineskris.github.io/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://ineskris.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://ineskris.github.io/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://ineskris.github.io/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Africa</title>
      <link>https://ineskris.github.io/project/dsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ineskris.github.io/project/dsa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Although microscopes are common in Uganda and other developing countries, a shortage of lab technicians to operate them means that access to quality diagnostic services is limited for much of the population. This leads to misdiagnoses of disease, which in turn causes life-threatening conditions to be incorrectly treated, drug resistance, and the economic burden of buying unnecessary drugs. Even where health facilities have lab technicians, they are often oversubscribed and have difficulty spending enough time on each sample to give a confident diagnosis. Given that smartphones are widely owned across the developing world, there is a technological opportunity to address this problem: phones can be used to capture and process microscopy images. This project aims to produce a functioning point-of-care diagnosis system on this principle, capable of running on multiple microscope and phone combinations. Our work exploits recent technological advances in 3D printing and deep learning to produce effective hardware and software respectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Step 1: Binary classification problem. You need to implement a machine learning model in order to classify whether a patch is positive or negative.
Step 2: Regression problem. You need to predict the number of parasites on each image (using model trained on Step 1).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hodgkin Huxley Model</title>
      <link>https://ineskris.github.io/project/hodgkinhuxley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ineskris.github.io/project/hodgkinhuxley/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Hodgkin–Huxley model, or conductance-based model, is a mathematical model that describes how action potentials in neurons are initiated and propagated. It is a set of nonlinear differential equations that approximates the electrical characteristics of excitable cells such as neurons and cardiac myocytes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhysioNet/Computing in Cardiology Challenge 2019</title>
      <link>https://ineskris.github.io/project/physionetcomputing-in-cardiology-challenge-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ineskris.github.io/project/physionetcomputing-in-cardiology-challenge-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sepsis is a life-threatening condition that occurs when the body&amp;rsquo;s response to infection causes tissue damage, organ failure, or death. In the U.S., nearly 1.7 million people develop sepsis and 270,000 people die from sepsis each year; over one third of people who die in U.S. hospitals have sepsis (CDC). Internationally, an estimated 30 million people develop sepsis and 6 million people die from sepsis each year; an estimated 4.2 million newborns and children are affected (WHO). Sepsis costs U.S. hospitals more than any other health condition at 24 billion dollars a year, and a majority of these costs are for sepsis patients that were not diagnosed at admission. Sepsis costs are even greater globally with the developing world at most risk. Altogether, sepsis is a major public health issue responsible for significant morbidity, mortality, and healthcare expenses.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenge Data Societé Generale</title>
      <link>https://ineskris.github.io/project/data-challenge-sg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ineskris.github.io/project/data-challenge-sg/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markov chains for detection of genetic motifs</title>
      <link>https://ineskris.github.io/project/markov-chains/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ineskris.github.io/project/markov-chains/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Election Analysis (2016)</title>
      <link>https://ineskris.github.io/project/americanelection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ineskris.github.io/project/americanelection/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have predicted that Hillary Clinton will win :/&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spread of COVID-19</title>
      <link>https://ineskris.github.io/project/covid19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ineskris.github.io/project/covid19/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
